# Edoardo Lanari

email: edoardo.lanari.el@gmail.com website: https://edolana.github.io

## Summary

Mathematician with over 4 years of experience in mathematical research. I have a strong scientific record, and I am now looking for applications of my skillset to a more applied, data-driven position in Data Science, Machine Learning or Quantitative Research.

#### Skills

• Higher Category Theory

• Homotopy Theory

• Python

• SQL

• (Topological) Data Analysis

• Algorithms and Data Structures

### Job Experience

2020present Lecturer in Object-Oriented Programming, Prague College.

2019present Postdoctoral Researcher in Mathematics, Institute of Mathematics CAS, Prague.

2018-2019

Lecturer in Mathematics at Charles University, Prague.

2015-2018

Teaching Assistant, Macquarie University, Sydney.

#### Education

2015-2018 2013-2015 PhD in Mathematics, Macquarie University Faculty of Mathematics and Statistics, Sydney. Double Master Degree in Mathematics, magna cum laude, University of Padova (Italy) and University of Leiden (The Netherlands).

2010-2013

BSc in Mathematics, magna cum laude, University of Trento, Italy.

For more information (scientific record, teaching material, etc...) please visit my website.